http://www.darwinplants.com/privacy-statement

Privacy statement
Privacy Policy
This document sets forth the DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. Online Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") for this Web site (the "Site"). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Site.
Changes in Privacy Policy
All "personal information" ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of the Site. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, such changes by your continued use of the Site after such notice has been posted for thirty (30) days with the following exception: If at the time you provide personal information to DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. you are given the opportunity (as you currently are) to limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. or by third parties, DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent.
Entities collecting personal information
Personal information on this Site is collected by DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V.
Veenenburgerlaan 108
2182 DC Hillegom
The Netherlands
Tel. +31 252 535 000
The Site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.
Collection of personal information
As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as subscribing to the collaboration services offered on the Site or utilizing online software applications, DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and fax numbers, and other personal information.
When you use the Site, DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. or third parties authorized by DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. may also collect certain technical and routing information about your computer to facilitate your use of the Site and its services. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer. We use these environmental variables to facilitate and track your use of the Site and its services. DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. also uses such environmental variables to measure traffic patterns on the Site. Without expressly informing you in each particular circumstance, we do not match such information with any of your personal information.
When you submit personal information to DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. through this Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices, including, without limitation, the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors of DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. Such vendors are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties.
DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. has established relationships with various service providers whose services are available to you from this Site or from Web sites that are linked to this Site. Typically, these providers offer services that DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. customers might find useful, such as those that can be used in conjunction with DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. services and products. In order to use those services, you may be required to provide personal information to the providers. Unless expressly provided to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a provider's Web site will be subject to the privacy policy posted on such site, and personal information that you provide while on this Site in conjunction with a provider's service will be subject to this Privacy Policy. You should be aware that our agreements with these service providers often provide that they will share with DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. personal information collected from you. In such instances, DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. may use this information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.
How your personal information is used
DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you subscribe to a service or register a product, for example, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. As another example, if you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. With you consent, your personal information may be used to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. and selected third parties.
DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. collects and maintains business information about its customers. All of the information gathered about our customers from any of the DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. Web sites is kept confidential, used for business purposes only and will not be sold to a third party.
For consumers and other users of any of the DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. Web sites, DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.
Your choices with respect to personal information
DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this Site. DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. will not communicate any information to you without your consent regarding products, services and special offers available from DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. If necessary, we reserve the right to communicate with you regarding your use of the services on this Site. Except in the particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. will also not provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent.
There are other instances in which DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. may divulge your personal information. DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. may provide your personal information if necessary, in DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V.'s good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations of a governmental or regulatory body or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant, or order or to protect the rights of DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. or others.
Protection of your personal information
The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. products or services or registering a DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. product is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Registration Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. In addition, your Registration Information resides on a secure server that only selected DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. personnel and contractors have access to via password. DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. encrypts your personal information and thereby strives to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V.
Personal information that you provide that does not constitute Registration Information also resides on a secure server and is accessible only to selected DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. personnel and contractors via password. Since this information is not accessible by you, you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information.
Use of cookies
When you visit this Site, you can browse the Site and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our Site, we use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, and enables DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. to record your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. (For some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)
While DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. uses cookies to track your visit to any of the DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. Web sites and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. does not use this information to identify you personally.
Personal information submitted through this Site that is not Registration Information is not accessible online. To access and/or correct such information, you may write DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. at:
DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V.
Veenenburgerlaan 108
2182 DC Hillegom
The Netherlands
In your correspondence, please indicate with as much detail as possible the location on this Site where you provided your personal information.
Privacy-related complaints
DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. has not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write the DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. Privacy Officer at the address indicated above.
In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. Online Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.
Please note that if you provide DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not), DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored.
Also, please note that DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. Web sites to which this Site or any other DARWIN PLANTS / WITTEMAN & CO. B.V. Web site may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites.
